paulstamatiou.com 2009-12-30

# Privacy Policy — PaulStamatiou.com

#### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, PaulStamatiou.com collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. PaulStamatiou.com’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how PaulStamatiou.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, PaulStamatiou.com may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

PaulStamatiou.com also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. PaulStamatiou.com does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

#### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to PaulStamatiou.com’s websites choose to interact with PaulStamatiou.com in ways that require PaulStamatiou.com to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that PaulStamatiou.com gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, visitors may choose to comment on an article and are asked to provide a name and email address. In each case, PaulStamatiou.com collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with PaulStamatiou.com. PaulStamatiou.com does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

#### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

PaulStamatiou.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on PaulStamatiou.com’s behalf or to provide services available at PaulStamatiou.com’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using PaulStamatiou.com’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. PaulStamatiou.com will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors, and affiliated organizations, as described above, PaulStamatiou.com discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when PaulStamatiou.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of PaulStamatiou.com, third parties, or the public at large. If you have subscribed to an article on PaulStamatiou.com or subscribed to the latest articles and have supplied your email address, PaulStamatiou.com may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with PaulStamatiou.com. If you send us a request, such as via the contact form on PaulStamatiou.com, we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users, unless you explicitly ask for the email to not be disclosed publicly. PaulStamatiou.com takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration, or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

#### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. PaulStamatiou.com uses cookies to help PaulStamatiou.com identify and track visitors, their usage of the PaulStamatiou.com website, and their website access preferences. PaulStamatiou.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using PaulStamatiou.com’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of PaulStamatiou.com’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, PaulStamatiou.com may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in PaulStamatiou.com’s sole discretion. PaulStamatiou.com encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

[](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/)Attribution for the above Privacy Policy goes to [Automattic’s Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/), protected under the Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 2.5 Generic license.
